Guide to the UTU Records
UTU Records
- Proposal to the Ohio Department of Transportation to Develop a Financing Alternatives Study for High Speed Passenger Development in Ohio (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Proposal to Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Technical Proposal to Study Financing Alternatives for High Speed Passenger Service Development in Ohio, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Feasible Financing Methods For High Speed Rail, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Feasible Financing Methods m For High Speed Rail (Box 96, Folder 11)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad Company -Merger- The New York Central Railroad Company (Box 96, Folder 12)
- "The Answer is Unity!" (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Rail Ohio, 1978-1979 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Strategy on Substance Use in Safety-Sensitive Positions in Canadian Transportation (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Ohio High Speed Rail Project (Box 96, Folder 16)
- The TGV Company Very High Speed Rail Proposal for Florida (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Newsletters (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 96, Folder 19)
- Award Circulars (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Award Circulars (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Ohio High Speed Rail (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Discussion of Intercity Rail Patronage Projection: Methodology and Selected Results (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Drugs and Drug Penalties Under Review: A Documentary Study (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Proceedings of the 1980 Conference Project REAP: A Report to the Industry (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Seminar on Measurement of Terminal Performance, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Portland Terminal Project: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Proposed Research Plan to Improve Railroad Employee Training (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Operation Redblock: Fourth Annual Chairpersons Conference, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Williamsport and Southern (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- 1976 Annual Report: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 97, Folder 12)
- A Cooperative Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Railroad Operations (Box 97, Folder 13)
- CSX Transportation Random Drug Testing Program as required by Federal Railroad Administration (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Buffalo Terminal Project Completion Report, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 15)
- Minutes of Task Force Meetings (Box 97, Folder 16)
- Rail Merger Study (Box 97, Folder 17)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 97, Folder 18)
- News (Box 97, Folder 19)
- Toward a Unified Transportation Policy (Box 97, Folder 20)
- Conrail Labor/Management Project Annual Report 1983 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- 1983 Final Report for the St. Louis Terminal Project (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Section I- Summary Evaluation and Recommendations, The Milwaukee Road Quality Circle Project, 1981-1983 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation Progress Reports (Box 98, Folder 4)
- "Nickel Rate Road" Safety Rules (Box 98, Folder 5)
- "Nickel Rate Road" The New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad Company (Box 98, Folder 6)
- "Nickel Rate Road" The New York, Chicago, and St. Louis Railroad Company (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company- Rules and Regulations for the Government of the Operating Department (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company- Safety Rules (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company- Safety Rules (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company- Safety Rules and Rules of General Conduct (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Wabash Railway Company- Rules and Regulations of the Transportation Department (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Wabash Railway Company- Rules of the Operating Department (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company- Rules and Regulations of the Operating Department, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company- Rules and Regulations of Operating Department (Box 98, Folder 15)
- Northern Pacific Railway Company. Rules and Regulations, Operating Department. (Box 98, Folder 16)
- The Oregon Railroad & Navigation Co. Rules and Regulations of the Operating Department (Box 98, Folder 17)
- Chicago Union Station Company Rules of the Operating Department (Box 98, Folder 18)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company Operating Rules (Box 98, Folder 19)
- Burlington Lines Rules of the Operating Department (Box 98, Folder 20)
- Erie Railroad Company Rules of the Operating Department, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 21)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company: Eastern and South-Central Districts and Idaho Division- Operating Rules (Box 98, Folder 22)
- The Consolidated Code of Operating Rules, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 23)
- Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1950 (Box 98, Folder 24)
- Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 25)
- Employee Assistance Program Burlington Northern Railroad (Box 98, Folder 26)
- "A Report on the United Transportation Union's 1970 Conference on Mass Transportation" (Box 98, Folder 27)
- 1970 (Box 98, Folder 28)
- Kansas City (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Brock Adams (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Proposed Qualification Requirements for Selected Railroad Jobs, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Maine Transportation, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Slurry Pipe Lines: Technological & Economic Description (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Report of Investigation by the Public Service Commission, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Offering Circular of Security by Transportation Company: Chicago and North Western Transportation Company (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Rail Lingo (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Intermodal (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Agreement Between Railroads Represented by the National Carriers' Committee and Employees of Such Railroads Represented by the United Transportation Union (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Due Process in Disciplinary Hearings (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Due Process in Disciplinary Hearings (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Field Manual- Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations (Box 99, Folder 13)
- OB Transit Technology (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Amtrak (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Task Force Meeting, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Task Force Meeting, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Task Force Meeting, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- "The Truth About American Ground Transport"- A Reply by General Motors (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Maps (Box 99, Folder 20)
- "Technology: The Lightning Rod, Ben Franklin and the Revolution." (Box 99, Folder 21)
- "Background" Vol. 22 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- The PANYC Merger (Box 99, Folder 23)
- News (Box 99, Folder 24)
- Yonder Comes the Train (Box 100, Folder 1)
- A Report on the United Transportation Union's 1970 Conference on Mass Transportation (Box 100, Folder 2)
- DOT Federal Railroad Administration (Box 100, Folder 3)
- National Transportation Trends and Choices (Box 100, Folder 4)
- PAT Co. -Air Controllers (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Rockets- Central Vermont (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Sprint (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Multi National Companies (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Coal Slurry Pipeline (Box 100, Folder 9)
- The 'Voracious Eleven' (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Award Circulars (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Agreements/ Disputes (Box 100, Folder 12)
- News (Box 100, Folder 13)
- Informational Pamphlets (Box 100, Folder 14)
- By Laws-Local 1393 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- "Handling Grievances: A Guide for Management and Labor" (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Synopsis of Project 27 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Conrail People Can Deliver (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Operation Redblock Member Folder (Box 101, Folder 4)
- "Railroad Freight Traffic Flows 1990 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Failing Railroads: Hearings before the Committee on Commerce United States Senate (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Failing Railroads: Hearings before the Committee on Commerce United States Senate, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Failing Railroads: Hearings before the Committee on Commerce United States Senate, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- The Move Toward Railroad Mergers: A Great National Problem (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Law and the National Labor Policy (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Studies Relating to Railroad Operating Employees (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Tolerance, Harmony and Progress- Proceedings of the Thirty-Third Convention of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Rail Lingo (Box 101, Folder 13)
- "Manpower Utilization in the Railroad Industry: An Analysis of Working Rules and Practices" (Box 101, Folder 14)
- "Progress Through Unity" (Box 101, Folder 15)
- "The Penn Central Failure and the Role of Financial Institutions, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Railroad Work Rules Dispute, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Intermodal Freight Program-Phase II Demonstration Management (Box 101, Folder 19)
- "Commission of Inquiry Hinton Train Collision" (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Misc. Reports (Box 101, Folder 21)
- Alcohol and Drugs (Box 101, Folder 22)
- The Railway Labor Executives' Association Employee Assistance Program Workshop (Box 101, Folder 23)
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 178 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Ton Mile Tax (Box 101, Folder 25)
- News (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Democracy in the Labor Movement (Box 101, Folder 27)
- "Background" (Box 101, Folder 28)
- (Box 101, Folder 29)
- Attendance Register B. of R.T. (Box 102, Folder 1)
- United States Transportation Maps (1 of 3) (Box 102, Folder 2)
- United States Transportation Maps (2 of 3) (Box 102, Folder 3)
- United States Transportation Maps (3 of 3) (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Milwaukee Intermodal Summary, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Competition Reports on Experiments (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Alcoholism Program (Box 103, Folder 3)
- National Council on Alcoholism (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Newsletters (Box 103, Folder 6)
- 1981 Conrail Performance Review (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Alcohol Related Accidents (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Reports and Agreements (Box 103, Folder 9)
- "The Potential Benefits of Railroad Facility Consolidation" (Box 103, Folder 10)
- "Freight Facility Compendium Network Projections Plans" (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Report and Recommendations of the UTU Study Commission Established by the Signatory Parties to the October 15, 1982 Agreement (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Terminal Experiment (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Commuter Railroad Feasibility Study on Selected Lines in the Los Angeles Metropolitan Area (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Railroad Work Rules (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Alaska RR (Box 103, Folder 16)
- Role of Gen. Sec. and Treas. (Box 103, Folder 17)
- 1969 Pay Schedules Gen. Chairmen (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Report to General Policy Committee Book No. 1 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- Report to General Policy Committee Book No. 2 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Memoranda of Conference (Box 103, Folder 21)
- Cherington Report- 1970 (Box 103, Folder 22)
- K.W. James, II (Box 103, Folder 23)
- S.B.A.-909 Award 96 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- (Box 103, Folder 25)
- The Government's Role in Public Transportation (Box 104, Folder 1)
- National Mediation Board: Fiftieth Annual Report, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Presidential Emergency Board No.219 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Before the Presidential Commission (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Improving Railroad Productivity (Box 104, Folder 5)
- A Study of Productivity Improvement Through Increased Employee Involvement, with Particular Emphasis on Ford Motor Company's Employee Involvement Process (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Report to The President by Emergency Board No. 212 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- News Clippings (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 212 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 211 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Report to the 99th Congress of the United States Second Session by Congressional Advisory Board (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Directory Switchmen's Union of North America--A.F.L.-C.I.O. and Ladies Auxiliary to the Switchmen's Union, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Wartime Wages and Railroad Labor (Box 104, Folder 12)
- 1000 Americans (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Handling Grievances: A Guide for Management and Labor (Box 104, Folder 14)
- The Story of a Steward (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Federal Aid to Railroads, Part III: Grants of Public Lands to Railroads (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Souvenir Program & Directory, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Federal Aid to Railroads, Part II: Government Capital Assistance Programs (Box 104, Folder 18)
- Directory Switchmen's Union of North America--A.F.L.-C.I.O. and Ladies Auxiliary to the Switchmen's Union (Box 104, Folder 19)
- Rail Lingo (Box 104, Folder 20)
- On the Track and Off the Train (Box 104, Folder 21)
- Operating Rules: Efficiency Test (Box 104, Folder 22)
- CSX Operating Rules: Efficiency Test, and Safety Handbook (Box 104, Folder 22)
- May '80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- June '80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- July '80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Aug. '80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Sept-Nov. '80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Dec. '80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Rock Island '79-'82, 1979-1982 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Rock Island 1982 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Summary of Selected Activities, 1978-1980 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Proposal for a Program of Experiments Involving Change in Operations in the Houston Railroad Terminal, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- A Cooperative Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Railroad Operations, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Final Report of St. Louis Terminal Project, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- 1976 Annual Report: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 105, Folder 14)
- A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Terminal Performance Measurement System, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- 1976 Annual Report: Task Force on Transportation (Box 105, Folder 17)
- 1978 Annual Report: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 105, Folder 18)
- A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Summary of Selected Activities (Box 105, Folder 21)
- RR Taxes '86, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Wage Rules, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Wage Rules- Emergency Board (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Remote Control Notice, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Carrier Work Rule Demands (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Carrier Sec. 6- 1984 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Milwaukee Road Quality Circles Project: Project Evaluation Report (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Agreement Questions (Box 106, Folder 8)
- HTP (Box 106, Folder 9)
- CR (Box 106, Folder 10)
- UP Meeting, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Diane Young (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Illinois Central (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Illinois Central (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Rail Perspective (Box 106, Folder 14)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 106, Folder 15)
- "Background" (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Agreement Between Chicago, Missouri and Western Railway Company and Its Employees Represented by the UTU (Box 106, Folder 17)
- The Ohio Association of Railroad Passengers (Box 106, Folder 18)
- A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 19)
- UTU Calendars (Box 106, Folder 20)
- Operation Redblock Member Folder (Box 106, Folder 21)
- Operation Redblock Work Book (Box 106, Folder 22)
- News (Box 106, Folder 23)
- Field Manual and Appendix (Box 106, Folder 24)
- New Political Thinking and the World Trade Movement (Box 106, Folder 25)
- Statement of Hon. W.G. McAdoo: Director General of Railroads before the Interstate Commerce Committee of the United States Senate, 1919 (Box 106, Folder 26)
- The UTU: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow (Box 106, Folder 27)
- Safety First (Box 106, Folder 28)
- Freedom of Speech and Press (Box 106, Folder 29)
- Collective Bargaining and Technological Change in American Transportation (Box 107, Folder 1)
- New Pressures on Collective Bargaining, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- The Forensic Quarterly of the Committee on Discussion and Debate the National University Extension Association, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- The Forensic Quarterly of the Committee on Discussion and Debate the National University Extension Association, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- The Forensic Quarterly of the Committee on Discussion and Debate the National University Extension Association, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Factors in Successful Collective Bargaining, 1951 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining or Monopoly (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Railroad Revitalization and Regulatory Reform Act of 1976 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- The Employer's Duty to Bargain: Counterproposal v. Concession (Box 107, Folder 9)
- The Effects of Need to Maintain Face on Interposal Bargaining (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Good Faith in Labor Negotiations: Tests and Remedies (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Collective Bargaining Techniques (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Las Vegas (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Operation Stop Chairpersons Conference, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Missouri State Legislative Board Legislative Report, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Operation Stop Chairpersons Conference, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- EAP Activity Reports 1972-86, 1972-1986 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- The Official Railway Guide (Box 107, Folder 18)
- National Intermodal Network (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Chicago Terminal Project (Box 107, Folder 20)
- Intermodal Freight Program-Phase II Demonstration Management, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- Intermodal Freight Program-Phase II Demonstration Management, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- Final Report of St. Louis Terminal Project, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation: Annual Report, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- 1976 Annual Report: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 107, Folder 25)
- News Clippings (Box 107, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Manual for Shop Stewards (Box 107, Folder 27)
- Work & Health. Its Your Life (Box 107, Folder 28)
- SSR Letter Index Vol. 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- SSR Letter Referee Index by Referee (Box 108, Folder 2)
- SSR Letter Referee Index by Subject (Box 108, Folder 3)
- (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Summation of O.L. Carter Investigation, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- CSX Random Drug Testing Program (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Award Circulars (Box 109, Folder 3)
- James R. Snyder Testimony (Box 109, Folder 4)
- 1987 Safety Assessments (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Blanchette FRH (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Northeast Rail Service Act 1981 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Union Shop (Box 109, Folder 8)
- S-P-Q: A Quality Circle Approach Designed for Conrail Mechanical Shops (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Labor Management Project- Buffalo Division, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- O.L. Carter Investigation (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Mini Pig (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Intermodal Proposals (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Misc. "Background" Vol. 9- Vol. 15 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Misc. "Background" Vol.16- Vol. 18 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Misc. "Background" Vol. 19- Vol. 22 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Agreements/ Statements (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Before Special Board 102-29 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- SEPTA Integrated Program (Box 110, Folder 2)
- 1976 Annual Report: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Report of the Presidential Railroad Commission, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Rail Service in the Midwest and Northeast Region: A Report by the Secretary of Transportation (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Employee Assistance Program: 1990 Annual and Cumulative Report (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Deferred Maintenance and Delayed Capital Improvements on Class II and Class III Railroads (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Congressional Record: Aid to Transportation (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations: Studies in Railroad Operations and Economics- Volume 8 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Report of General Secretary and Treasurer, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Constitution, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- "The Progressive" (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Car Utilization: Final Task Force Report Recommended Research Program (Box 110, Folder 13)
- "Background" Vol. 23, No. 3, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Western Railroad Mergers (Box 110, Folder 15)
- CSX (Box 110, Folder 16)
- DW Collins (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Reliability in Railroad Operations: Executive Summary, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- The Economics of Unit Trains (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Magazines (Box 110, Folder 20)
- Important Information: What Every UTU Family Should Know (Box 110, Folder 21)
- Correspondence (Box 110, Folder 22)
- News (Box 110, Folder 23)
- News (Box 110, Folder 24)
- News (Box 110, Folder 25)
- Port Terminal Railroad: Rules and Regulations (Box 110, Folder 26)
- 1990 Report (Box 110, Folder 27)
- Historic Railroads (Box 110, Folder 28)
- Transatlantic Crisis: Europe and America in the '70's (Box 110, Folder 29)
- Awards- P.L.B. (Box 111, Folder 1)
- SSR Letter Index Volume I (Box 111, Folder 2)
- SSR Letter Index Volume III (Box 111, Folder 3)
- SSR Letter Index Volume IV (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Railroad Slang (Box 112, Folder 1)
- New Jersey- Indiana- Illinois (Box 112, Folder 2)
- General Organizers (Box 112, Folder 3)
- NMB Representation Manual (Box 112, Folder 4)
- TPW, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Organizing Material (Box 112, Folder 6)
- UTU Organizing Position- Short Lines (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Hardin Letter on Organizing Shortline (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Prevention Pipeline (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Energy Studies (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Energy Crisis (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Energy Crisis (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Preliminary System Plan (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Final System Plan (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Final System Plan (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Pass PUMAS Congress, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- CSX and Railway Unions: In Search of New Solutions (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Ohio High Speed Rail Passenger Plan (Phase 1), 1977 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Preliminary Draft "Rail Ohio" The Rail Plan for Ohio, 1978-1979 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Conrail Meeting, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- SP-L-M Task Force (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Kate Shelley (Box 113, Folder 10)
- St. Louis- Task Force (Box 113, Folder 11)
- United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit (Box 113, Folder 12)
- Misc. "Background" (Box 113, Folder 13)
- News/ Information (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 113, Folder 15)
- United Transportation Union Member Packet (Box 113, Folder 16)
- United Transportation Union Member Packet (Box 113, Folder 17)
- Letters to Members of the Board (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Du Bose- Hardin (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Correspondence- Senator Wheeler, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- United Labor Agency, Inc. (Box 114, Folder 4)
- 1977 Inaugural Committee (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Mobility 2000: Moving Wisconsin into the 21st Century (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Freight Rail Policy Plan: Draft for Public Review (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Section I Summary Evaluation and Recommendations: The Milwaukee Road Quality Circle Project, 1981-1983 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- 1983 Final Project for the St. Louis Terminal Project (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Wage and Rules Work Book, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- 1984 Wage Rule Proposals (Box 114, Folder 11)
- Wage and Rules Correspondence, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- Wage and Rules Correspondence, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 13)
- The "Do" Lines (Box 114, Folder 14)
- Color Enlargement (Box 114, Folder 15)
- Summation of the Marrill Arnold Investigation, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 16)
- "Progress Through Unity" Proceedings of the Sixth Convention of the United Transportation Union (Box 114, Folder 17)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 114, Folder 18)
- Research and Agreements (Box 114, Folder 19)
- News (Box 114, Folder 20)
- "Background" Vol. 13 No. 5 (Box 114, Folder 21)
- A Local Chairman's Handbook (Box 114, Folder 22)
- SU of NA (Box 114, Folder 23)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Brakemen, Proceedings of the First Annual Convention, 1884 (Box 114, Folder 24)
- Brakeman's Manual (Box 114, Folder 25)
- National Railroad Passenger Corporation: Operating Rules and Instructions (Box 114, Folder 26)
- Conrail '85, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Conrail 1985 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Conrail Acquisition, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Conrail Acquisition, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- 1984 (Box 115, Folder 5)